<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Taj Mumbai</string>
    <string name="about_history">The Taj Mahal Palace opened in Mumbai, then Bombay, in 1903, giving birth to the country’s first harbour landmark. The flagship hotel of Taj Hotels, Resorts and Palaces overlooks the majestic Gateway of India.This legendary luxury hotel has played host to kings, dignitaries and eminent personalities from across the globe, and is acknowledged as a world leader in hospitality. Each of the 550 rooms and suites between the palace and tower wing is a striking blend of nostalgic elegance, rich history and modern facilities.</string>
    <string name="about_location">Strategically located in Mumbai’s prime historical and commercial hub, The Taj Mahal Palace is walking distance from Colaba Causeway, known for its touristy tiny roadside shops. The city’s financial hub, parliament, stadium, offices and shopping districts are all located within close proximity; as is a flourishing art and heritage precinct with must visit museums, art galleries, churches and synagogues. The airports are an hour away.</string>
    <string name="about_cuisines">For those who would like to experience fine dining in style, we host 10 of the city’s most acclaimed restaurants and bars, renowned for delectable cuisines from India, Europe, the Middle East and the Orient. Relish authentic Indian cuisine at Masala Kraft; world famous Japanese dishes at Wasabi by Morimoto; exquisite Eastern Mediterranean at Souk and Chinese at Golden Dragon.Dine all day at Shamiana and choose from the exotic range of sumptuous desserts at La Patisserie. Unwind with a refreshing meal at Aquarius, the poolside restaurant;and visit the stylish Harbour Bar.</string>
    <string name="about_facilities">Signature experiences such as the afternoon tea at Sea Lounge and private dining at the Chef’s Studio make your stay with us truly memorable.Mumbai’s original luxury hotel has 11 newly refurbished halls and venues, ideal for occasions ranging from formal meetings to elaborate weddings. The Ballroom, spacious enough for 450 guests, is perfect for conferences and grand private events.You could opt for a private dinner or yacht party if you are looking to entertain in true style. Our globally acclaimed Golden Keys Concierge would be happy to help, and caters to all your requirements in the city. Come, experience the legend.</string>
    <string name="about_company">Taj Hotels Resorts and Palaces is recognized the world over for delivering a unique flavor of hospitality that offers world-class refinement while remaining deeply rooted in its Indian heritage. For more than a century, Taj has brought together the unique beauty and traditions from across India in an experience that highlights true Indian hospitality. This draws on the time-honored traditions central to the Indian homecoming, from the refreshing simplicity of the welcome drink to the careful choreography of the dinner service. Taj has helped to put many Indian destinations on the map. From the resorts of Goa to the upcoming business hubs of India’s Silicon Valley, an iconic Taj hotel is a mainstay of the destination. By providing jobs to the local community, supporting endangered artisan practices and reviving regal history at palaces where royal families are still in residence, Taj offers a rare insider’s point of view to the fascinating story of India – from Maharaja to modern day. With 98 hotels in 62 locations across India, Taj offers guests the refined luxury of heritage combined with effortlessly efficient service and local expertise to create a moment to remember. In India, Taj hotels are strategically located to offer the Taj experience in business hubs, industrial towns and metropolises, as well as the most remote pilgrimage centers, historic and natural destinations. The group has extended its international presence with 15 hotels in the Maldives, Malaysia, the UK, USA, Bhutan, Sri Lanka, Africa and the Middle East.</string>
    <string name="address">Apollo Bunder, Mumbai\nMaharashtra, India - 400 001</string>
    <string name="taj_email">tmhbc.bom@tajhotels.com</string>
    <string name="at_a_glance">At A Glance</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="cuisines">Cuisines</string>
    <string name="facilities">Facilities</string>
    <string name="book_your_stay">Book Your Stay</string>
    <string name="book_now">Book Now</string>
    <string name="select_a_room_suite">Select a Room/Suite:</string>
    <string name="no_of_children">Number of Children (0 &#8211; 12 Years)</string>
    <string name="no_of_adults">Number of Adults (12+ Years)</string>
    <string name="check_out_date">Check-Out Date</string>
    <string name="check_in_date">Check-In Date</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="postal_address">Postal Address</string>
    <string name="get_in_touch">Get In Touch</string>
    <string name="taj_phone">+91 22 6665 3366</string>
    <string name="taj_fax">+91 22 6665 0300</string>
    <string name="we_are_social">We Are Social</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="taj_website"><u>taj.tajhotels.com</u></string>
    <string-array name="rooms_list">
        <item>Tower Superior Rooms</item>
        <item>Tower Deluxe Rooms</item>
        <item>Luxury Grande Rooms</item>
        <item>Taj Club Rooms</item>
        <item>Executive Suites</item>
        <item>Luxury Suites</item>
        <item>Grand Luxury Suites</item>
        <item>Ravi Shankar Suite</item>
        <item>The Tata Suite</item>
        <item>Rajput Suite</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
